Hsuan-Chung, Wang

EMAIL: jeremy4555@yahoo.com.tw

MOBILE PHONE: 0921687452

ADDRESS: 12F.-1, NO.30, SEC. 2, ZHONGSHAN RD., ZHONGHE DIST., NEW TAIPEI CITY 235, TAIWAN (R.O.C.)

SUMMARY

Hard-working and quick-learning data engineer focusing on NLP model research and implementation. 1+ year experience developing various kinds of applications using NLP techniques including deep learning models, machine learning models, chatbots, visualization projects and websites. Experience in implementation of DNN, RNN, LSTM and GAN... algorithms. Bachelor's degree experience in tax and 5+ years' experience in debate club. In addition, proficient in business process flows, in logical thinking and in oral presentation.

EDUCATION

Sep 2016 – Present	National Chenchi University, Taipei (Taiwan), Master of Law and Inter-Discipline
Sep 2015 – Jan 2016	Xiamen University, Xiamen (China), Accounting Exchange Student
Sep 2012 – Jun 2016	National Taipei University, New Taipei (Taiwan), Bachelor of Art in Public Finance
WORK EXPERIENCE	
Dec 2017 - Present	Python Developer, Freelancer, Part-time, Machine learning(NLP), Chatbots and Websites
Apr 2016 – Jul 2016	Tax assistant, Grant Thornton Taiwan, Part-time, compilation of Transfer pricing report
SKILLS	
Software	NLP(DNN, RNN, LSTM, GAN, IR), Data (ML, DL, Keras, tensorflow, sklearn, web
	crawling), Database (SQL, NoSQL), Cloud Platform(AWS, Azure, GCP), Frontend (html,
	CSS, JavaScript, jQuery), Backend (Django)
language	English: IELTS 6.5 (L:6.5 S:6 R:6 W:7)

PROJECTS AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Innovex AI+ Solution Match (2018)

- Provided AI solutions including product recommendation system and fake recruit message detect system.
- Superior Technique Award

Patent Keywords Recommendation System (2018), Link

- Assistance in locating related patent keywords for retrieval of relevant patents
- train word2vec model using 39 million patent specifications

SimCorpFinder(2017), Link

- comparable company retrieval system
- saved 1/3 the time for the task of finding comparable companies

kaggle Mercali Suggestion Challenge (2017), Link

- used RNN+LSTM model to provide price suggestions for second-hand products sellers
- Beat around 80% teams globally

Hsinchu Government Line Bot (2017), Link

- government information searching system with machine learning classification model helping transport questions to the person in charge
- 99% classification precision, 2nd place in Hsinchu Open Data Hackathon

iThome Ironman Competition - AI & Machine Learning (2017), Link

- wrote 30+ NLP and machine learning articles
- up to 30 thousand people browsing

CASA Big Data Marketing Competition (2016)

- predicted consumer consuming behavior
- gave advice on Marketing strategy
- silver award

National Debate Competitions

1st Place x 2, 2nd Place x 3, 4th Place x 1, Best Debater x 5, Excellent Instructor x 1

ESSAY

- State Administration of Taxation, China. (2016). <u>The investment guidance of taxation in Philippine for Chinese resident</u>¹ (in charge of China-Philippine Tax Treaty section, p88-109)
- Hsuan-Chung Wang. (2015). China-Taiwan Tax Treaty context analysis. Jiuzhoupress (九州出版社).

¹ http://www.chinatax.gov.cn/n810219/n810744/n1671176/n1671206/c2352695/part/2352710.pdf